https://fuel180.com/privacy.aspx

Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative site, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative collects personally identifiable information, such as your email
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This
information is used by Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
does not read any of your private online communications.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
and Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative collects and uses your personal information to operate the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative and its affiliates. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative, in order to determine what Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative pages, or
register with Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative site or services, a cookie helps Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact Web design and hosting, e-marketing, graphic design and interactive development | Fuel180 Creative at chris@cdmeyer.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
Terms Of UsePrivacy StatementCopyright 2020 by C. D. Meyer, Inc.
Back To Top
